[
  {
    "question": "What is Oppa real name?",
    "answers": ["Sergey", "Oppa", "孔子", "Baby"],
    "correct": [0],
    "multipleChoice": false
  },
  {
    "question": "When Oppa was born?",
    "answers": ["17.07.2000", "07.17.2000", "17.04.2003", "yesterday"],
    "correct": [0, 1],
    "multipleChoice": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Pick Oppa favorite food from the list.",
    "answers": ["Pizza", "Pasta", "宝宝", "KFC"],
    "correct": [0, 1, 2, 3],
    "multipleChoice": true
  },
  {
    "question": "What Oppa has Master degree with honors at?",
    "answers": ["Being cute and horny", "Radio engineering (Remote sensing)", "Cooking", "Physical education"],
    "correct": [1],
    "multipleChoice": false
  },
  {
    "question": "What type of Oppa does NOT exist?",
    "answers": ["Cute Oppa", "Horny Oppa", "Angry Oppa", "Bald Oppa"],
    "correct": [3],
    "multipleChoice": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which country Oppa would like to travel first?",
    "answers": ["USA", "UAE", "China", "Mongolia"],
    "correct": [2],
    "multipleChoice": false
  },
  {
    "question": "What would be the best Christmas present for Oppa?",
    "answers": ["Sport car", "New graphic card", "My baby smile", "New Balance sneakers"],
    "correct": [2],
    "multipleChoice": false
  },
  {
    "question": "At what speed can a mosquito typically travel?",
    "answers": ["5 m/s", "10 m/s", "0.5 m/s", "3.364353453 m/s"],
    "correct": [2],
    "multipleChoice": false
  },
  {
    "question": "关于中国历史上的\"十六国\"时期，下列哪个政权并非由鲜卑族建立？",
    "answers": ["前燕（由慕容部鲜卑建立）", "后赵（由羯族建立）", "南燕（由慕容部鲜卑建立）", "西秦（由乞伏部鲜卑建立）"],
    "correct": [1],
    "multipleChoice": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Do you love Oppa?",
    "answers": ["Yes", "Definitely", "Absolutely", "NO"],
    "correct": [0, 1, 2],
    "multipleChoice": true
  }
]
